https://www.denverda.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Translate This Website
Select LanguageAfrikaansAlbanianAmharicArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBengaliBosnianBulgarianCatalanCebuanoChichewaChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CorsicanCroatianCzechDanishDutchEnglishEsperantoEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchFrisianGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekGujaratiHaitian CreoleHausaHawaiianHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIcelandicIgboIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseJavaneseKannadaKazakhKhmerKoreanKurdish (Kurmanji)KyrgyzLaoLatinLatvianLithuanianLuxembourgishMacedonianMalagasyMalayMalayalamMalteseMaoriMarathiMongolianMyanmar (Burmese)NepaliNorwegianPashtoPersianPolishPortuguesePunjabiRomanianRussianSamoanScottish GaelicSerbianSesothoShonaSindhiSinhalaSlovakSlovenianSomaliSpanishSudaneseSwahiliSwedishTajikTamilTeluguThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduUzbekVietnameseWelshXhosaYiddishYorubaZulu
FacebookTwitterEmail
Privacy Policy
Copyright
All content © 2017 District Attorney's Office of Denver, Colorado and its representatives. All rights reserved.
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations, and software, is the property of the Denver District Attorney’s Office, Colorado or its content suppliers and is protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive property of the Denver District Attorney, Colorado and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of Denver District Attorney, Colorado or its software suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws.
Information Collection and Retention
For the purposes of this statement “personally identifiable information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual who is the subject of the information. For the purposes of this statement, “District Attorney” means the Office of the District Attorney for the 2nd Judicial District of the State Of Colorado, employees of that office, and any persons contracted to provide services for that office.
Individuals do not have to provide personally identifiable information to visit the District Attorney’s Internet Portal to read, download or print information. The District Attorney may request personally identifiable information from you in order to be able to answer questions, give you information, and to provide specific services that you request. Any information collected for that purpose would be only that which is necessary to provide those purposes and will be handled as it would be on an in-person visit to a government office.
In order to provide new services, design a more customer-friendly website and facilitate access to the website and other services provided by the District Attorney, the District Attorney analyzes traffic on the all of its websites and web pages. Information that is not personally identifiable, such as web pages or services accessed, IP (Internet Protocol) addresses, date, time, and browser types/versions is collected and used for this purpose. The District Attorney does not attempt to associate this data with information that is personally identifiable (such as an e-mail address).
Cookies
The District Attorney does not monitor your web-browsing activities with cookies. However, cookies may be used by some applications on the District Attorney website (e.g. property search, listserver, e-commerce, etc.) when necessary to complete a transaction, to process data submitted to us online, or to pass information from one Web page to another. If you choose to share personal information, such as sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, this information will be used to fulfill the request for which the information was submitted, and may be stored and shared pursuant to data storage/privacy policies, statutes, and governing law. Information may be shared with anyone employed or contracted to provide services to the District Attorney.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Use of E-Mail Addresses of Persons Accessing This Website
E-mail addresses obtained as a result of a request to the District Attorney’s website will not be sold or given to other private companies for marketing purposes. E-mail or other information requests sent to the website may be maintained in order to respond to the request or to forward the request to the appropriate personnel within the District Attorney’s office or other appropriate governmental agency, employee, or contractor. Individuals may be able to receive updates on issues important to them, but only if they choose to “opt-in” to that specific service. By “opting-in” to one such service they do not “opt-in” to other services. Should they subsequently choose not to receive such informational updates via e-mail they can remove themselves at any time.
Personally Identifiable Information Available on Governmental Websites
All content contained within or associated with the District Attorney website is subject to the provisions of the Colorado Public (Open) Records Act, §24-72-201 et.seq., C.R.S., as amended. Information that is not confidential and is available during an in-person visit to a government office may be posted for electronic access through District Attorney’s Internet portal.
Online Profiling is the practice of aggregating information about the preferences and interests of individuals, gathered primarily by tracking their movements online and using the resulting citizen profiles to create targeted content on websites. The District Attorney’s Office does not conduct or participate in online profiling.
Advertising
All forms of advertising are prohibited on the District Attorney’s website.
Content Disclaimer
The District Attorney has used all reasonable efforts to ensure that the pages and other information on this website do not contain any inaccurate information.  However, we can make no guarantees or warranties as to the accuracy or the timeliness of the data. If you believe any material contained in this website is inaccurate, please call us at 720-913-2000.
The District Attorney’s Office reserves the right to make changes, corrections and/or improvements at any time and without notice. In addition, the District Attorney disclaims any and all liability for damages incurred directly or indirectly as a result of errors, omissions or discrepancies. This site is provided “as is” without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied. You should not assume that this site is error-free or that it will be suitable for the particular purpose which you have in mind when using it. In no event shall the District Attorney be liable for any special, incidental, indirect or consequential damages of any kind, or any damages whatsoever, including, without limitation, those resulting from loss of use, data or profits, whether or not advised of the possibility of damage, and on any theory of liability, arising out of or in connection with the use or performance of this site or other documents which are referenced by or linked to this site.
Linkage Policy
The District Attorney’s website, www.denverda.org any domain names that point to sites therein are provided as a public service. The sites are overseen by the District Attorney’s Information Technology Department but are managed by specific individuals or divisions within the District Attorney’s office. The District Attorney makes no representations, guarantees, or warranties as to the accuracy, completeness, currency, or suitability of the information provided via the website. The District Attorney specifically disclaims any and all liability for any claims or damages that may result from providing the site or the information it contains, including any websites maintained by third parties and linked to the District Attorney’s website. The responsibility for content rests with the organizations that are providing the information. The inclusion of links from these sites does not imply endorsement by the District Attorney. Specific questions regarding any content should be directed to the appropriate organization. The District Attorney makes no effort to independently verify, and does not exert editorial control over, information on pages outside of the District Attorney’s website. The District Attorney does not endorse any of the products, vendors, consultants, or documentation referenced in this website. Any mention of vendors, products, or services is for informational purposes only. Linking to the District Attorney’s website is permitted under limited conditions. If you link to this site, you may not portray any person or subject in a false or misleading light. You must also refrain from creating frames, or using other visual altering tools, around the District Attorney’s Office pages. Lastly, you may not imply that the District Attorney is endorsing your product or services.
Data Security and Quality
The District Attorney’s Office is committed to security and accuracy of personally identifiable data that is either available from or collected by governmental websites, and has taken reasonable precautions to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration. Any third parties responsible for this information are committed to the same principles, and also are required by contract to follow the same policies and guidelines as the District Attorney’s Office in protecting this information. Unless otherwise prohibited by state or federal law, rule or regulation, the individual has the right to have personally identifiable information that is inaccurate corrected.
Warning
Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this website, including unauthorized alterations to the wording of any online forms available on the site, are strictly prohibited. Alteration of the wording of downloadable or online forms renders the forms invalid. Unauthorized interference with the operations and functions of this website, by electronic or other means, is strictly prohibited. Any attempt to use any information, feature, or other aspect of the site to engage in criminal conduct will be vigorously prosecuted. Any unlawful actions may be subject to criminal prosecution under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986, and other criminal laws, and may also result in civil liability.
ShareTweet
